BRUNO SALA

Full Stack Software Engineer PHP, Node oriented stacks brunosala.com

Hello! My name is Daniel Bruno Sala, I'm a self-starting Full Stack Developer based out of Chicago, IL. I've worked with a diverse array of clients from various countries on projects that range from simple website development to enterprise-scale application engineering. My goal is to deliver high quality, bold products to my clients all while having a bit of fun.

I attribute my success as a software engineer to having strong algorithm development and technical communication skills. Being able to pass on not only the solution but the "recipe" to the solution offers much more than just a deliverable.

CONTACT

Email: connect@brunosala.com Phone: +1 (513) 668-7678 Location: Greater Chicago Area

FRONT END

SCSS CSS in JS, React-JSS tailwindcss JavaScript, TypeScript Angular 2+, RxJS React, Redux Webpack, Rollup.js NX, Create React App

BACK END

PHP 5-8 Laravel, Symfony mySQL/MariaDB PostgreSQL WordPress, Drupal, Joomla

Node.js, Express Gatsby, Next.js GraphQL MongoDB, DynamoDB

DEVOPS

Apache, NGINX Docker Kubernetes AWS Jenkins, Terraform

EDUCATION

Associate's Degree in Management and Information Systems

REFERENCES

Corey Simpson - COO ILTA corey@iltanet.org

Phillip Bergner - CTO All Digital Solutions phil@alldigitalsolutions.com

CONNECT

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/brunosala

RECENT EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Software Engineer

Allbound

Contributor to new product features, legacy code management and upcycling, and project management for application framework.

- Interviewing and onboarding of new engineers
- Majority code review contributor
- Designed a front end framework project placing a majority of the legacy code base in a modern scaleable toolchain.
- Orchestrated aforementioned projects; scheduled meetings with stakeholders, designed workbooks, decision documents, and telephone logs

Front End Angular Developer

Oct 2018 - April 2020

Aug 2020 - Present

International Legal Technology Association

Lead the development on new websites and new mobile applications utilizing Angular 2+ as well as assisting in a large scale data migration into Salesforce.

- Utilized Angular 2+, Apache Cordova, and Force.js to build and deploy single page applications to browser, Android, and iOS
- Set up automated testing for the Angular UIs using Karma
- Performed peer code review
- Assisted in the migration of 30+ years worth of customer data into Salesforce CRM
- Created automated tests to validate migration data
- Reviewed and documented solutions submitted for task and bug tickets in Jira

Front End JavaScript Developer

June 2018 - Jan 2019

Equiti Games - Contract

- Designed and developed ICO website front end.
- Provided marketing strategy in the form of email campaign automation, SEO, automated blog / site content, and social media management.

Full Stack LAMP Developer

June 2016 - Oct 2018

The Creative Group

Interviewed clients, created project management documentation, and led development on various client LAMP based projects.

- Enabled my clients by providing specification and scope documents, setting timelines, defining budgets and leading development
- ☐ Built four WordPress sites, two Laravel Applications, two e-commerce platforms
- Each individual client project lasted roughly three to six months

Full Stack JavaScript Developer

June 2018 - Jan 2019

BitBlog - Contract

- Designed and developed ICO Website front end.
- ☐ Built blockchain-based e-commerce platform based on Ethereum transactions.
- ☐ Utilized Asana to post project deadlines and progress.